mp3rocket.com 2016-03-31

# MP3 Rocket - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We prepared this Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy (which is incorporated herein) to explain to you how and why we collect Personal Information about you when you are using our Platform.

The Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy are a part of the Terms and are incorporated therein by references. The definitions which appear in this document shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms.

When you use the Platform, you consent to the collection, storage, use, disclosure and other uses of your Personal Information (meaning, any information which may potentially allow your identification with reasonable means) as described in this Privacy Policy. If we combine Personal Information with anonymous information about you, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined.How do we receive information about you?

We receive information (including Personal Information) about you from various sources:

•If you voluntarily provide us your personal details within the Platform (for example by registering to create a MP3Rocket Account or by subscribing to our newsletter);

•If you use or access our Platform (for example by visiting our Website or the Embedded Items, by contributing content to our Platform or by clicking on certain content or on advertisements);

•From third party websites and services (for example we may receive information from the websites, social network platforms or applications on which the Embedded Items are included).

What kinds of information do we collect?

Depending on which features of the Platform you use, we collect different kinds of information (including Personal Information) about or from you.

•When you register to create a MP3Rocket Account in our Platform –

We collect the information you provide when you sign up to our Platform. This can include your name, email address, your photograph and other information you provide. If you register to our Platform through a social network platform (for example Facebook or Google+), you will provide us access to any information you made available on that platform, (depending on your privacy settings) and any additional information that you specifically consent to provide us with.

•When you interact with content on our Platform – 

We collect certain information about you when you interact or engage with content made available on our Platform. This includes information about the websites and apps you visit (including the Website, the Embedded Items, the Applications and any Third Party Content), your use of the content displayed on the Platform (including your clicks on answers to questions presented and other information that you submit), your use of the advertisements displayed on the Platform (including your clicks on advertisements) as well as information the developer or publisher of the website or app provides to us.

•When you contribute User Content to our Platform – 

We collect the User Content that you publish or contribute to our Platform (for example comments that you have posted, or content that you have uploaded through your MP3Rocket Account). If your use of our Platform includes certain financial transactions (for example, if you are an advertiser, publisher, partner or customer, with whom we have contractually engaged) we collect information about the transaction. This can include your payment information (for example your credit card number and other card information), billing, and contact details, as well as other authentication information.

•Log data and device information – 

We automatically record and collect certain Personal Information from or about your device (for example your computer or your mobile device) when you install our Application or access our Platform (for example when you visit our Website) or when you interact with our content (including when you visit the Embedded Items). This includes information about your operating system version, IP address, GCM Registration ID, device settings, hardware information, device approximate location, mobile operator or internet service provider information, browser type, language preferences, time zone, domains that referred you to our Platform (for example the HTTP referrer and URL) and the duration of your visits, your actions on these visits (for example clicks or views on content on the domain, or interactions with social media features). We may also automatically collect your device geo-location. When you are using our Application, we also automatically record your Google Advertising ID (if you are using an Android device) or your advertising Identifier (IDFA – if you are using an iOS device), for advertising purposes. The Google Advertising ID is an anonymous identifier, provided by Google Play services. If your device has an Advertising ID, we collect and use it for advertising and user analytics purposes. By downloading or using our Application, you explicitly agree that we may associate your Advertising ID with your applicable persistent device identifier. This will facilitate our ability to improve your personalized experience. Further, we may use other persistent identifiers for non-advertising purposes. If your device does not have Advertising ID, we will use other persistent identifiers. The information collected may be also stored on your device.

•When you communicate with us (for example when you send us an email with a comment or feedback) we collect the Personal Information you provided us with.

•We also collect information (including Personal Information) about you from third parties, for example our business partners, for marketing purposes and to deliver products or services you request.Tracking technologies and cookies

When you visit or access our Platform (for example when you visit our Website, visit the Embedded Items or download our Application), or when you interact or engage with Third Party Content, we use (and authorize third parties to use) web beacons, cookies, pixel tags, scripts, tags and other technologies ("Tracking Technologies").

The Tracking Technologies allow us to automatically collect information about you and your online behavior, as well as your device (for example your computer or mobile device), in order to enhance your navigation on our Platform, improve our Platform's performance and customize your experience on our Platform. We also use this information to collect statistics about the usage of our Platform, perform analytics, deliver content which is tailored to your interests and administer services to our Users, advertisers, publishers, customers and partners.

In addition, we may merge information we have with information collected through Tracking Technologies and with information we may obtain from other sources and, as a result, such information may become Personal Information.

We also allow third parties to collect information about you through Tracking Technologies. This information is anonymized and cannot identify you, and is used for marketing and ad-targeting purposes. To learn more please visit our Cookie Policy.

How do we use the information we collect?

•Improve and personalize your experience on our Platform 

We work hard to provide you with a fun and engaging experience on our Platform. In order to do so we use all of the information that we have (including your Personal Information) to create a personalized experience for our Users and to improve our Platform. For example, we can suggest content that you might like (such as movie polls or sports surveys) based on your activity on our Platform.

•Surveys and research 

We are always trying to think of new and exciting features for our Users. From time to time, we conduct surveys or test features in our Platform, and analyze the information we have to develop, evaluate and improve these features.

•Service-related updates 

We use the information that we have to let you know about our policies or important notifications and updates about our Platform. For example, if you have provided us with your email address, we may use it to alert you about upcoming articles, features or events. If you have a MP3Rocket Account, we may use your email address to alert about our new features, or to send you reminders to complete activities that you’ve started on our Platform or to remind you of your password (if you've forgotten it). We will also send recommendations of additional content that you may like. You can also subscribe to receive notifications concerning certain content on our Platform (for example new posts or results) or to receive updates about new items on certain channels.

•Communication

We use the information that we have to communicate with you – for example, we will use your email address to respond to your queries or feedback.Advertising 

We also use and share non-Personal Information (meaning, aggregated information or Personal Information which is de-identified and cannot allow the identification of a User) we have, including information collected through our Tracking Technologies, with our partners (in various jurisdictions around the world) for advertising purposes.Opt-out

If you do not want us to use or share your Personal Information (namely, information which can potentially identify you) for advertising purposes, you may opt-out in accordance with this "Opt-out" section. Please note that even if you opt-out, we may still use and share your Personal Information with third parties for non-marketing purposes (for example to fulfill your requests, communicate with you and respond to your inquiries, etc.). In such cases, the companies with whom we share your Personal Information are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these non-marketing services.

You can turn off the third party cookies for advertising purposes by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative.

•Direct marketing

If you subscribed to our newsletter (by submitting your email address) you will receive free audience engagement tips and announcements straight to your email account. We may also send you promotional material, either concerning the Platform or our partners' marketing products, which we believe may interest you. You may choose not to receive our promotional or marketing emails (all or any part thereof) by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that you receive from us. Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our newsletter, we may continue to send you service-related updates and notifications.

•Protecting rights

We will also use and disclose your information (including your Personal Information) to investigate violations and enforce our policies, and as required by law, regulation or other governmental authority, or to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate any fraud, security or technical issues, or respond to a government request. We also reserve the right to disclose any information in case we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is appropriate or necessary in order to enforce our Terms, take precautions against liabilities, investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, protect the security or integrity of the Platform and our servers and protect the rights and property of MP3Rocket, its users and/or others.With whom do we share the information that we collect?

We share your information that we collect (including your Personal Information, and information collected through Tracking Technologies) for the purposes listed above with our affiliates, partners and other trusted businesses and individuals that provide us, or to which we provide a variety of services, such as publishers and advertisers that work with us, developers and service providers who process such information for us, so they can help us provide and improve our services. By accessing the Platform, you acknowledge and agree that these trusted third parties are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services. We may also share non-Personal Information with our partners, publishers and advertisers, for advertising purposes.

Please remember that the content that you submit to the Platform, including your User Content, comments you post on our Platform and content you submit to your MP3Rocket Account profile page, is accessible to anyone on the Internet. Please avoid submitting any content that is private or confidential, or any content that you do not want to be used and viewed by others. You are solely responsible for any legal or other repercussions that occur as a result of your User Content, and we do not assume any responsibility or liability which may arise from your User Content.International data transfer

Please note that our businesses, as well as our trusted partners and service providers, are located around the world. Any information that we collect (including your Personal Information) is stored and processed in various jurisdictions around the world (including in the United States), for the purposes detailed in this Privacy Policy. By using or accessing this Platform, you consent to your information being collected, used, and transferred as disclosed herein. The data protection and other laws of these jurisdictions may not be as comprehensive as those in your country – but we will accord by the terms of this Privacy Policy.Mergers and acquisitions

We may share or transfer your information (including Personal Information) if we enter into a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or sale of some or all of our assets. Any party that acquires our assets as part of such a transaction may continue to use your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.Children privacy

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. By accessing or using our Platform, you certify to us that you are at least 13 years old. The Platform and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. We respect the privacy of parents and children and are committed to complying with the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). If you are under the age of 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, then please contact us at support@MP3Rocket.com.Information collected by third parties

Some content, features or products on our Platform may link to or be hosted on or sponsored by third parties who may obtain Personal Information from you if you voluntarily submit such information or participate (for example, if you click on an advertisement or choose to participate in their activities, such as sweepstakes and promotions or if you provide any payment information as detailed above, or if you upload your CV on our career page). When you provide your Personal Information to such third parties, you allow them to collect, keep, manage use and disclose such information, and you also agree to be bound by their privacy policy which will detail how you may exercise your choice regarding your Personal Information. We cannot be responsible for any information collected by such third parties, or their privacy practices. Therefore, you should always review their privacy practices carefully before providing Personal Information to such third parties.User choice

You may access, update, and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information which is in our control by emailing us at support@MP3Rocket.com or by otherwise changing the information on your MP3Rocket Account profile page. We may request certain Personal Information from you for the purposes of verifying your identity.

If you ever decide to terminate your MP3Rocket Account, you may do so by emailing us at support@MP3Rocket.com.

If you terminate your MP3Rocket Account, any Personal Information that you have provided us will no longer be accessible via your MP3Rocket Account. However, given the nature of the Platform, any public activity on your MP3Rocket Account prior to deletion will remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public. In addition, any content that you have published or contributed to our Platform (for example your User Content) will remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public.

While we have no obligation to remove content once published on our Platform, you may request that we remove or delete your Personal Information from our Platform by emailing us at support@MP3Rocket.com.Retention

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to provide our services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies.Security

We have implemented administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, use, or disclosure of your Personal Information. 

Your MP3Rocket Account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to help us prevent unauthorized access to your MP3Rocket Account by protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your account by signing off after you have finished accessing your MP3Rocket Account. 

You will be solely responsible for keeping your password confidential and for all use of your password and your MP3Rocket Account, including any unauthorized use. While we seek to protect your information to ensure that it is kept confidential, we cannot guarantee the security of any information. You should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the internet and that there is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of your 

Personal Information or other content you transmit using the Platform, and you do so at your own risk. Thus, we encourage you to exercise discretion regarding the Personal Information you choose to disclose.Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, in our sole discretion, and the most current version will always be posted on our website (as reflected in the "Last Revised" footer). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. By continuing to access or use the Platform after any revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the new Privacy Policy, please stop accessing or using the Platform.Have any questions or comments? Contact us!

If you have any comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, you can always contact us at support@MP3Rocket.com.MP3Rocket Support

701 Rossland Road East Ste 363  
Whitby, Ontario L1N 9K3  
CanadaRevised at: Feb 15th 2016
